You read the comments set by Mayuresh Joshi sir last
night and Neeraj ji
's comment according to which you see Nifty back
becoming a difficult thing, a little bit of
Berenice and time correction coming in the market,
tell me what two things do you
think will help the market to rise on
which traders and investors
can have confidence that even if the market falls, they should
buy there, that
Muslims are giving good morning, so
set the minutes of typing which have come
and those who are carrying infection,
they did not have this setting that
their rate is tax cycle, tell me, at the same time it is
quite khelo, GDP is estimated at
6 and a half to 7 percent, which is the
unemployment figure, yes, for the market, they have
kept that 4% pack constant, so
keep it somewhere that colony, you expect to
grow and develop a good place to connect
with Doctor saheb, we have seen the introduction effect,
things are very different, there has been a
little trick on this, there has definitely been some turmoil,
definitely a botanical survey was done, Rajwat  The problem is
dollar demand, this lipid acid, only so there could be a
slight setback in the emerging market on this,
but I don't see this player
Gurjar correction, so two things you were asking about censor,
one I think pinched off
spirit is Indian Oil Corporation, quite
Vidya thing, I've been quite amazing, I slipped on
operating in the first quarter, the last
quarter numbers will be a little soft
but not as compared to transform like
recovery we have to see, I think the
second speaker which will be very very good,
only so this decision star co-workers, second I was
that Nitish's poll aspirations and
terms of volunteers, visited
market, solving market share,
if you press India, then India needs right after
effects, then say that your breast
solid combined, after follow will start coming back
because their number in terms of
investment and investment
opportunities, there are a lot of options with the fans,
not that
this, then you are seen setting the strategy in front of you, the enthusiasm you are seeing
Maya,
in this downturn, if you like any good fundamental counter that has come in front of you in the last one or two
days,
where
you saw good technical branch backs coming,
instead of strong printing, pay
more
attention to the general insurance place in the next few days. Chanel Life Insurance
for General Vaidya Year Border, our team
feels that the class may be 5th century, although
according to these data it is a little down, but
we feel that the position is in term for
third party motor insurance, Sushma Health
Insurance for Fire Insurance, against
private space, fit office number one piece
Valentine, it has combined graduate level,
international support in all this, this cream sir
2012 sent some serious 12596 balance stand
on bus stand, which accused it has 2819 percent, the
current investment will be seen, depression
scientists researchers and don't time sir, so a
very good property, placid and quite
honest politician could have won, which
turns out well, fatal attraction, so because of this, it will
conceive vitamin Academy Award, a
good momentum plate, the
best leading general insurance
company of 20, I would like in the private sector space
Do our research for free with Mayuresh Joshi